{
    "id": "ff849ef0030642deb41aa834c5afb890",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I …………………… be happy to meet Robinson.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "shall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ff9ff921a082461ba677587db13c1a0d"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… he play for our team?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Shall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4157b95da5a74a26ae3dbba491c29f40"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… I get a prize if I stand first in the examination?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Would",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f425fef797c64da9bb1591046e24719b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. be able to beat him. (Express possibility)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "could",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "51d77f68bd644ffabe8fc516489b2076"
        },
        {
            "question": "Watch and pray lest you …………………. fall into temptation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "85e7f825e60647e69441478ad4fe6deb"
        },
        {
            "question": "The old man ………………… recline in a corner and sleep most of the time. (Express a habitual action in the past)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f775cef4e60448a18a557cdde00864e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… rather read a novel than watch that stupid movie.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "899fa787945a4bf9971d5d7febb863e3"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… you mind lending me your pen for a minute?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should",
                "Could"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4a3424367944483f930c80a46188c875"
        },
        {
            "question": "Till last year, I ………………. read without glasses.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dc863c21aec04a2e85d49e972a4659f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I ……………….. fly like a bird, I …………………. be with you now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "could, would",
                "would, would",
                "could, should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e7edc1b8492840b59f46de04bffe21a0"
        }
    ]
}